Guide to the M. L. Rosenthal Papers ca. 1930-1996 MSS 45 MSS.045
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Subject Files
  - Subseries A: writers and artists
    - Gregory, Lady, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 36)
    - Grieve, Christopher, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 37)
    - Gurthrie, Ramon, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 38)
    - H, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 39)
    - Harrison, Jim, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 40)
    - Holloway, John, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 41)
    - Horovitz, Michael, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 42)
    - Hoskins, Katherine, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 43)
    - Hughes, Ted, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 44)
    - I, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 45)
    - J, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 46)
    - Joyce, James, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 47)
    - K, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 48)
    - Kavanagh, Patrick, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 49)
    - Kinnell, Galway, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 50)
    - Kinsella, Thomas, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 51)
    - Kizer, Carolyn, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 52)
    - L, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 53)
    - Laing, Alexander, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 54)
    - Laing, Dilys, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 55)
    - Laughlin, James, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 56)
    - Lawrence, D. H., undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 57)
    - Levertov, Denise, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 58)
    - Lowell, Robert, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 59)
    - M, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 60)
    - Mc, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 61)
    - MacNeice, Louise, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 62)
    - Merriam, Eve, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 63)
    - Merwin, W. S., undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 64)
    - Montague, John, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 65)
    - Mottram, Eric, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 66)
    - Moore, Marianne, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 67)
    - Muir, Edwin, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 68)
    - Muir, Kenneth, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 69)
    - Murphy, Richard, undated; 31142040612056 (Box III.A.1, Folder 70)
    - N, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 71)
    - Nemerov, Howard, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 72)
    - O, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 73)
    - Olson, Charles, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 74)
    - P, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 75)
    - Parra, Nicanor, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 76)
    - Plath, Sylvia, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 77)
    - Pound, Ezra, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 78)
    - Pound, Ezra, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 79)
    - Pound, Ezra, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 80)
    - Q, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 81)
    - R, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 82)
    - Rago, Henry, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 83)
    - Redgrove, Peter, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 84)
    - Riding, Laura (Jackson), undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 85)
    - Roethke, Theodore, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 86)
    - Rosenthal, David, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 87)
    - Rudman, Mark, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 88)
    - Rudnick, Raphael, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 89)
    - Rukeyser, Muriel, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 90)
    - S, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 91)
    - Schevill, James, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 92)
    - Schulman, Grace, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 93)
    - Scott, Winfield Townley, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 94)
    - Seferis, George, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 95)
    - Shapiro, Karl, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 96)
    - Shelton, Richard, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 97)
    - Simpson, Louis, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 98)
    - Smith, A. J. M., undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 99)
    - Spender, Stephen, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 100)
    - Stendhal, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 101)
    - Stevens, Wallace, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 102)
    - T, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 103)
    - Thomas, Dylan, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 104)
    - V, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 105)
    - W, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 106)
    - Walker, Ted, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 107)
    - Weiss, Theodore, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 108)
    - Whittemore, Reed, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 109)
    - Wilbur, Richard, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 110)
    - Williams, Tennessee, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 111)
    - Williams, William Carlos, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 112)
    - Wilson, Edmund, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 113)
    - Wright, David, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 114)
    - Wright, James, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 115)
    - XYZ, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 116)
    - Yeats, W. B., undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 117)
    - Unidentified subjects, undated; 31142040612064 (Box III.A.2, Folder 118)
  - Subseries B: General
    - Advice to PMLA, etc., undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 1)
    - Aesthetics, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 2)
    - African literature, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 3)
    - American literature (general), undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 4)
    - Anthologies (poetry), undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 5)
    - Anthologies (war poetry), undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 6)
    - Art, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 7)
    - Background on pre-modern poets, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 8)
    - Background on prose writers, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 9)
    - BBC, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 10)
    - BBC broadcast and other radio, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 11)
    - Behavior, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 12)
    - Bibliographies, reading lists, etc., undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 13)
    - Brighton festival, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 14)
    - Children's work, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 15)
    - Civil liberty (academic liberties debate), undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 16)
    - Classical literature, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 17)
    - Conference materials, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 18)
    - Criticism, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 19)
    - Documents, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 20)
    - Drugs, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 21)
    - Eastern European and Russian literature, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 22)
    - Ecology, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 23)
    - Education, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 24)
    - Education-English Department, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 25)
    - Exams (undergraduate), undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 26)
    - French literature, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 27)
    - Germany, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 28)
    - Ireland, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 29)
    - Israeli literature, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 30)
    - Juvenilia (1942-43), 1942-1943; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 31)
    - Kavanagh's Weekly, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 32)
    - Latin American and Spanish literature, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 33)
    - Lectures and articles, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 34)
    - Lectures and articles, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 35)
    - Lectures and articles, undated; 31142040612072 (Box III.B.3, Folder 36)
    - Lecture notes, exams, syllabi, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 37)
    - Lectures, talks, broadcasts, readings, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 38)
    - Linguistics and language, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 39)
    - Literary history-19th century, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 40)
    - Literary history-20th century, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 41)
    - Literary theory, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 42)
    - Literature and philosophy, religion, myth, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 43)
    - Literature and politics, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 44)
    - Literature and psychology, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 45)
    - Literature and science, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 46)
    - Microfilm, etc., undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 47)
    - Misc. notes, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 48)
    - Misc. notes, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 49)
    - Misc. poems, essays, lectures, etc., undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 50)
    - Misc. reviews (mixed) pre-1960, 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 51)
    - Misc. reviews (mixed) 1960-64, 1960-1964; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 52)
    - Misc. reviews (mixed) 1965-69, 1965-1969; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 53)
    - Misc. reviews (mixed) 1970-74, 1970-1974; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 54)
    - Notebook of poems (MLR), undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 55)
    - Notes on current poetry, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 56)
    - NYU-English programs, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 57)
    - NYU-English programs (Sumner, Ives), undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 58)
    - Old English, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 59)
    - Oriental literature, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 60)
    - P.E.N., undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 61)
    - Periodicals, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 62)
    - Philosophy, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 63)
    - Pinocchio conference, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 64)
    - Poetry-definitions, attributes, etc., undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 65)
    - Poetry-teaching of, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 66)
    - Poetry-tone, voice, readings, etc., undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 67)
    - Poets-general, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 68)
    - Pre-modern English language (A - M), undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 69)
    - Pre-modern English language (N - Z), undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 70)
    - Present Tense, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 71)
    - Publicity (MLR non-book-related), undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 72)
    - Radio, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 73)
    - Rockland Country Day School, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 74)
    - Scholarly studies and lectures (Wycherly, Poe, etc.), undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 75)
    - Surrealism-poetry, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 76)
    - Translation, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 77)
    - Typography, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 78)
    - Voice of America, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 79)
    - War/politics, undated; 31142040612080 (Box III.B.4, Folder 80)
- Series IV: M.L. Rosenthal's writing
  - Subseries A: book-related
    - Effective Reading (1944), 31142040612098 (Box IV.A.1, Folder 1)
    - Exploring Poetry, first edition (1955), 31142040612098 (Box IV.A.1, Folder 2)
    - Exploring Poetry (1955), 31142040612098 (Box IV.A.1, Folder 3)
    - Exploring Poetry (1955), 31142040612098 (Box IV.A.1, Folder 4)
    - Exploring Poetry (1955), 31142040612098 (Box IV.A.1, Folder 5)
    - Exploring Poetry (1955), 31142040612098 (Box IV.A.1, Folder 6)
    - Exploring Poetry (1955), 31142040612098 (Box IV.A.1, Folder 7)
    - Exploring Poetry, second edition (1973), 31142040612098 (Box IV.A.1, Folder 8)
    - A Primer of Ezra Pound, ms. (1960), 31142040612098 (Box IV.A.1, Folder 9)
    - A Primer of Ezra Pound, reviews and correspondence (1960), 31142040612098 (Box IV.A.1, Folder 10)
    - The Modern Poets, Chapter 1, ms. (1960), 31142040612098 (Box IV.A.1, Folder 11)
    - The Modern Poets, Chapter 2, ms. (1960), 31142040612098 (Box IV.A.1, Folder 12)
    - The Modern Poets, Chapter 3, ms. (1960), 31142040612098 (Box IV.A.1, Folder 13)
    - The Modern Poets, Chapter 4, ms. (1960), 31142040612098 (Box IV.A.1, Folder 14)
    - The Modern Poets, reviews and correspondence (1960), 31142040612098 (Box IV.A.1, Folder 15)
    - Chief Modern Poets, fourth edition (1962), 31142040612098 (Box IV.A.1, Folder 16)
    - Chief Modern Poets (1962), 31142040612098 (Box IV.A.1, Folder 17)
    - Chief Modern Poets (1962), 31142040612098 (Box IV.A.1, Folder 18)
    - Chief Modern Poets, fourth edition (1962), 31142040612106 (Box IV.A.2, Folder 19)
    - Chief Modern Poets (1962), 31142040612106 (Box IV.A.2, Folder 20)
    - Chief Modern Poets (1962), 31142040612106 (Box IV.A.2, Folder 21)
    - Chief Modern Poets (1962), 31142040612106 (Box IV.A.2, Folder 22)
    - Chief Modern Poets (1962), 31142040612106 (Box IV.A.2, Folder 23)
    - Chief Modern Poets (1962), 31142040612106 (Box IV.A.2, Folder 24)
    - Chief Modern Poets, fifth edition (1970), 31142040612106 (Box IV.A.2, Folder 25)
    - Chief Modern Poets, sixth edition, undated; 31142040612106 (Box IV.A.2, Folder 26)
    - Selected Poems and... of William Butler Yeats (1962), 31142040612106 (Box IV.A.2, Folder 27)
    - Blue Boy on Skates, ms. (1964), 31142040612106 (Box IV.A.2, Folder 28)
    - Blue Boy on Skates, ms. (1964), 31142040612106 (Box IV.A.2, Folder 29)
    - Blue Boy on Skates (1964), 31142040612106 (Box IV.A.2, Folder 30)
    - Blue Boy on Skates (1964), 31142040612106 (Box IV.A.2, Folder 31)
    - The William Carlos Williams Reader (1966), 31142040612106 (Box IV.A.2, Folder 32)
    - The New Poets, ms. (1967), 31142040612114 (Box IV.A.3, Folder 33)
    - The New Poets, ms. (1967), 31142040612114 (Box IV.A.3, Folder 34)
    - The New Poets, ms. (1967), 31142040612114 (Box IV.A.3, Folder 35)
    - The New Poets, ms. (1967), 31142040612114 (Box IV.A.3, Folder 36)
    - The New Modern Poetry (1967), 31142040612114 (Box IV.A.3, Folder 37)
    - The New Modern Poetry, permissions and correspondence (1967), 31142040612114 (Box IV.A.3, Folder 38)
    - The New Modern Poetry, permissions/paperback (1969), 31142040612114 (Box IV.A.3, Folder 39)
    - 100 Postwar Poems (1968), 31142040612114 (Box IV.A.3, Folder 40)
    - 100 Postwar Poems (1968), 31142040612114 (Box IV.A.3, Folder 41)
    - Beyond Power, ms. (1969), 31142040612114 (Box IV.A.3, Folder 42)
    - Beyond Power, ms. (1969), 31142040612114 (Box IV.A.3, Folder 43)
    - Beyond Power (1969), 31142040612114 (Box IV.A.3, Folder 44)
    - Beyond Power, review, correspondence, etc. (1969), 31142040612114 (Box IV.A.3, Folder 45)
    - Randall Jarrell (1972), 31142040612114 (Box IV.A.3, Folder 46)
    - The View from the Peacock's Tail, ms. (1972), 31142040612114 (Box IV.A.3, Folder 47)
    - The View from the Peacock's Tail (1972), 31142040612114 (Box IV.A.3, Folder 48)
    - The View from the Peacock's Tail (1972), 31142040612114 (Box IV.A.3, Folder 49)
    - The View from the Peacock's Tail, reviews, etc. (1972), 31142040612114 (Box IV.A.3, Folder 50)
    - Poetry and the Common Life, correspondence and permissions (1974), 31142040612114 (Box IV.A.3, Folder 51)
    - Poetry and the Common Life, reviews and publicity (1974), 31142040612114 (Box IV.A.3, Folder 52)
    - She, ms. (1977), 31142040612122 (Box IV.A.4, Folder 53)
    - She (1977), 31142040612122 (Box IV.A.4, Folder 54)
    - She, reviews and publicity (1977), 31142040612122 (Box IV.A.4, Folder 55)
    - Sailing Into the Unknown (1978), 31142040612122 (Box IV.A.4, Folder 56)
    - Sailing Into the Unknown, correspondence, reviews, publicity, etc. (1978), 31142040612122 (Box IV.A.4, Folder 57)
    - Poems 1964-1980, Oxford UP publicity and correspondence (1981), 1964-1980, 1981; 31142040612122 (Box IV.A.4, Folder 58)
    - Poems 1964-1980, reviews and publicity (1981), 1964-1980, 1981; 31142040612122 (Box IV.A.4, Folder 59)
    - The Adventures of Pinocchio (1983), 31142040612122 (Box IV.A.4, Folder 60)
    - The Adventures of Pinocchio, correspondence (1983), 31142040612122 (Box IV.A.4, Folder 61)
    - The Adventures of Pinocchio, reviews and publicity (1983), 31142040612122 (Box IV.A.4, Folder 62)
    - Pinocchio (1983), 31142040612122 (Box IV.A.4, Folder 63)
    - Pinocchio (1983), 31142040612122 (Box IV.A.4, Folder 64)
    - Pinocchio (1983), 31142040612122 (Box IV.A.4, Folder 65)
    - Pinocchio (1983), 31142040612122 (Box IV.A.4, Folder 66)
    - Pinocchio (1983), 31142040612122 (Box IV.A.4, Folder 67)
    - Pinocchio (1983), 31142040612122 (Box IV.A.4, Folder 68)
    - The Modern Poetic Sequence (1983), 31142040612130 (Box IV.A.5, Folder 69)
    - The Modern Poetic Sequence, correspondence (1983), 31142040612130 (Box IV.A.5, Folder 70)
    - The Modern Poetic Sequence, reviews and publicity (1983), 31142040612130 (Box IV.A.5, Folder 71)
    - The Modern Poetic Sequence, ms. (1983), 31142040612130 (Box IV.A.5, Folder 72)
    - The Modern Poetic Sequence, ms. (1983), 31142040612130 (Box IV.A.5, Folder 73)
    - The Modern Poetic Sequence, ms. (1983), 31142040612130 (Box IV.A.5, Folder 74)
    - The Modern Poetic Sequence, ms. (1983), 31142040612130 (Box IV.A.5, Folder 75)
    - The Modern Poetic Sequence, galley (1983), 31142040612130 (Box IV.A.5, Folder 76)
    - The Modern Poetic Sequence, galley (1983), 31142040612130 (Box IV.A.5, Folder 77)
    - The Modern Poetic Sequence, proofs (1983), 31142040612130 (Box IV.A.5, Folder 78)
    - The Modern Poetic Sequence, proofs (1983), 31142040612130 (Box IV.A.5, Folder 79)
    - The Modern Poetic Sequence, proofs (1983), 31142040612130 (Box IV.A.5, Folder 80)
    - The Modern Poetic Sequence, paperback (1985), 31142040612130 (Box IV.A.5, Folder 81)
    - The Poet's Art, ms. (1987), 31142040612130 (Box IV.A.5, Folder 82)
    - The Poet's Art, ms. (1987), 31142040612130 (Box IV.A.5, Folder 83)
    - The Poet's Art, correspondence, reviews, publicity (1987), 31142040612130 (Box IV.A.5, Folder 84)
    - Poetry In English, introduction (1987), 31142040612130 (Box IV.A.5, Folder 85)
    - Poetry In English, correspondence, etc. (1987), 31142040612130 (Box IV.A.5, Folder 86)
    - As for Love, drafts (1987), 31142040612130 (Box IV.A.5, Folder 87)
    - As for Love, reviews and publicity (1987), 31142040612130 (Box IV.A.5, Folder 88)
    - Our Life in Poetry (1991), 31142040612130 (Box IV.A.5, Folder 89)
    - Our Life in Poetry, correspondence, reviews, publicity (1991), 31142040612130 (Box IV.A.5, Folder 90)
    - "Works-In-Progress" Ploughshares 17 (MLR guest editor), correspondence (1991), 31142040612148 (Box IV.A.6, Folder 91)
    - "Works-In-Progress" Ploughshares 17, correspondence, reviews, publicity (1991), 31142040612148 (Box IV.A.6, Folder 92)
    - Running to Paradise (1994), 31142040612148 (Box IV.A.6, Folder 93)
    - Running to Paradise, reviews and publicity (1994), 31142040612148 (Box IV.A.6, Folder 94)
    - In the World Pub, ms. (1995-96), 1995-1996; 31142040612148 (Box IV.A.6, Folder 95)
    - In the World Pub (1995-96), 1995-1996; 31142040612148 (Box IV.A.6, Folder 96)
    - In the World Pub (1995-96), 1995-1996; 31142040612148 (Box IV.A.6, Folder 97)
    - In the World Pub, drafts of sequence (1995-96), 1995-1996; 31142040612148 (Box IV.A.6, Folder 98)
    - In the World Pub (1995-96), 1995-1996; 31142040612148 (Box IV.A.6, Folder 99)
    - In the World Pub (1995-96), 1995-1996; 31142040612148 (Box IV.A.6, Folder 100)
    - In the World Pub (1995-96), 1995-1996; 31142040612148 (Box IV.A.6, Folder 101)
    - In the World Pub (1995-96), 1995-1996; 31142040612148 (Box IV.A.6, Folder 102)
    - In the World Pub, drafts of poems not used? (1995-96), ?1995-1996; 31142040612148 (Box IV.A.6, Folder 103)
    - In the World Pub, drafts of recent poems (1995-96), 1995-1996; 31142040612148 (Box IV.A.6, Folder 104)
    - Misc. book-related, undated; 31142040612148 (Box IV.A.6, Folder 105)
    - Notes towards book for Oxford (not written), undated; 31142040612148 (Box IV.A.6, Folder 106)
    - Notes and correspondence towards revised edition of Chief Modern Poets (not published), undated; 31142040612148 (Box IV.A.6, Folder 107)
    - Possible book project, undated; 31142040612148 (Box IV.A.6, Folder 108)
  - Subseries B: essays, poems, reviews, lectures
    - Classroom notes, undated; 31142040612155 (Box IV.B.7, Folder 1)
    - Classroom notes, undated; 31142040612155 (Box IV.B.7, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence re: essays, introductions, forewords, etc., undated; 31142040612155 (Box IV.B.7, Folder 3)
    - Dissertation: "Chief Poets of the American Depression", undated; 31142040612155 (Box IV.B.7, Folder 4)
    - Dissertation, undated; 31142040612155 (Box IV.B.7, Folder 5)
    - Dissertation, undated; 31142040612155 (Box IV.B.7, Folder 6)
    - Dissertation, undated; 31142040612155 (Box IV.B.7, Folder 7)
    - Dissertation, undated; 31142040612155 (Box IV.B.7, Folder 8)
    - Editorship-Macmillan, undated; 31142040612155 (Box IV.B.7, Folder 9)
    - Editorship-Maximum Security Ward, reviews and correspondence, undated; 31142040612155 (Box IV.B.7, Folder 10)
    - Editorship-The Nation, correspondence, undated; 31142040612155 (Box IV.B.7, Folder 11)
    - Editorship-Present Tense, correspondence, undated; 31142040612155 (Box IV.B.7, Folder 12)
    - Engagements, undated; 31142040612155 (Box IV.B.7, Folder 13)
    - Essays (A), undated; 31142040612155 (Box IV.B.7, Folder 14)
    - Essays (B-D), undated; 31142040612155 (Box IV.B.7, Folder 15)
    - Essays (E-I), undated; 31142040612155 (Box IV.B.7, Folder 16)
    - Essays (L-M), undated; 31142040612155 (Box IV.B.7, Folder 17)
    - Essays (N), undated; 31142040612155 (Box IV.B.7, Folder 18)
    - Essays (O), undated; 31142040612155 (Box IV.B.7, Folder 19)
    - Essays (P), undated; 31142040612163 (Box IV.B.8, Folder 20)
    - Essays (Q-S), undated; 31142040612163 (Box IV.B.8, Folder 21)
    - Essays (T-Z), undated; 31142040612163 (Box IV.B.8, Folder 22)
    - Essays (pre-1950), 31142040612163 (Box IV.B.8, Folder 23)
    - Essays (1950-1959), 31142040612163 (Box IV.B.8, Folder 24)
    - Essays (1960-1969), 31142040612163 (Box IV.B.8, Folder 25)
    - Essays (1970-1979), 31142040612163 (Box IV.B.8, Folder 26)
    - Essays in progress, undated; 31142040612163 (Box IV.B.8, Folder 27)
    - Forewords, undated; 31142040612163 (Box IV.B.8, Folder 28)
    - Interviews, undated; 31142040612163 (Box IV.B.8, Folder 29)
    - Introductions, undated; 31142040612163 (Box IV.B.8, Folder 30)
    - Introductions (reviews and correspondence), undated; 31142040612163 (Box IV.B.8, Folder 31)
    - Lectures / Readings, undated; 31142040612163 (Box IV.B.8, Folder 32)
    - Lectures / Readings, undated; 31142040612163 (Box IV.B.8, Folder 33)
    - Lectures / Readings, undated; 31142040612163 (Box IV.B.8, Folder 34)